https://www.stamps.com/privacy-policy/do-not-sell-my-personal-information/

Home
Privacy Policy
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
When you use Stamps.com, you are trusting us with your information.
We take protection of your information seriously and are committed to ensuring the security of all customer data.
New privacy regulations now require businesses like Stamps.com to give consumers a process for opting out of any potential practice where customer personal information might be sold. Although we do not sell personal information for monetary value, our actions may be considered a “sale” under the CCPA.
For further information on our privacy practices, please review our Privacy Policy or contact us at
1-888-434-0055.
Formally record your preference that Stamps.com not sell your personal information by filling out the form.
First name
Last name
Email
Phone
STATE OF RESIDENCE
Alabama
Alaska
American Samoa
ZIP CODE OF RESIDENCE
ACCOUNT NUMBER/USERNAME (OPTIONAL)
×Close
Your Stamps.com OfferService Fee and Trial DetailsIf you stay with Stamps.com past the trial period, you will be charged $17.99 a month plus applicable taxes, if any, for the Stamps.com service, including the first month. You can cancel your services at any time.FREE 5lb Digital ScaleAs a new Stamps.com customer you will receive a FREE 5 lb. Digital Scale. The scale is a $50 value and is yours to keep with no additional obligation. Just pay for shipping and handling (typically $9.99 or less).$25 Postage OfferAs a new Stamps.com customer you will receive $5 in free postage that you can use during your trial period. After you complete your trial period, you are eligible for an additional $20 in postage. We will give you two $10 postage coupons. You can redeem one coupon per month once you complete your trial.FREE Supplies KitTo help you get started we will ship you a free Supplies Kit that includes free postage labels to use with the service (a $5 value). However, you don't need to wait for the Supplies Kit to arrive in order to print postage. You can immediately take advantage of features such as printing shipping labels on plain paper or printing postage directly on envelopes!
